pixect.com 2014-12-01

# Pixect.com - Privacy Policy & Terms of Service

This Privacy Policy sets out the data processing practices carried out through the web by the Pixect website. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us at info@pixect.com.

## Information collected

Protecting your personal privacy is very important to us, Pixect.com collects no personal information about you other than website usage data and that which you choose to provide when you use the website. No individual identifying or personal information (such as your name or email) is automatically gathered when you visit Any Page of Pixect.com.

## Webcam Data

Information about your webcams and images captured are not transferred outside your computer unless you choose to download or publish/upload on Facebook, Twitter or Tumblr. When you upload a picture to some social networking websites using Pixect, it might go through our server(s) and kept there temporarily for technical reasons. That temporary data is stored without your personal information and cleared within few hours by an automated process.

## Use of personal information by Pixect.com

We process your personal information for the purposes of providing and personalising our services and providing you with information about products and services offered by us. Your peronal information such as IP address, geographic location and language is collected and used by Pixect website to provide you a customized experience. We may also use and disclose information in aggregate (so that no individuals are identified) for marketing and strategic development purposes.

Your personal data may be used for legal purposes in court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from its improper use.

## Disclosures

We will only disclose personal information to other companies within our group of companies and successors in title to our business, unless otherwise agreed.

## Use of personal information by 3rd parties

Your information will never be passed to any 3rd party outside the Pixect.com.   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Use of cookies

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. Pixect.com website might use cookies to remeber your website usage preferences.

## Other web sites

Our web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you that will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

## Facebook

Pixect.com allows you to connect with your Facebook account and perform certain actions. When you authorize Pixect Facebook application, it may publish content on your behalf and collect your personal information like id, name, picture, gender and locale. This website and the Facebook application is not developed by Facebook.

## Twitter

Pixect.com allows you to connect with your Twitter account and perform certain actions. When you authorize Pixect Twitter application, it may tweet content on your behalf and collect your personal information like name, surname etc.

## Internet-based transfers

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by using our website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.

## Terms of Service

The materials contained in the Pixect website are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.

Don't use Pixect to take photos that could be construed in any way as porn, copyrighted material, harassment, or spam. If you do, your access to the services will be restricted. The service is for personal and non-commercial use only.

## Limitations

The Pixect service is for personal and non-commercial use only. In no event shall Pixect.com or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on the Pixect.com website.
